Vincent Patrick Castro

vincentxpatrick@gmail.com | 0967-296-0756 | Cuatro de Julio St., Santo Niño, Quezon City

PROFILE

I am excited to start a fulfilling profession that will allow me to have a significant impact on the technology industry. I am sure that my technical expertise and strong work ethic will help me succeed in a demanding and exciting working setting.

EDUCATION AND HONORS

Polytechnic University of the Philippines, Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2019 - 2023 Cum Laude

- Dean's Lister A.Y. 2019-2020
- President's Lister A.Y. 2020-2021
- Dean's Lister A.Y. 2021-2022
- Dean's Lister A.Y. 2022-2023

Nueva Ecija Senior High School, Senior High School

2017 - 2019

• Academic Excellence Award with Honors A.Y. 2018-2019

Nueva Ecija High School, High School

2013 - 2017

• Academic Excellence Award with Honors A.Y. 2016-2017

EXPERIENCE

Safe – Midman App

November 2023 – December 2023

Frontend Developer

- Develops user interface for the mobile, and web app
- Manual tests the apps

AHG Lab March 2023 – June 2023

Frontend Web Development Intern

• Responsible for developing user interface for websites, making the page responsive.

SKILLS

- Programming: JavaScript, ReactJS, NextJS, HTML5, CSS/ Tailwind, PHP
- Database Management: SQL, MySQL, SQL SERVER (e.g., create databases/ tables, execute queries)
- **No-code Development:** FlutterFlow

PROJECTS

Park-King: A Reservation-based and Recommending Parking Mobile Application

• Full Stack Web Developer for our content management system

Beds and Rooms: A property rental system

• Frontend Web Developer

Safe – Midman App & Safe – Admin Web

• Frontend Developer